YASMIN **CASTRO**

FULL-STACK

PERSONAL INFO

ADDRESS

Goiânia - Brazil

PHONE

+55 62 98169 5581

E-MAIL

yasminsdcastro@gmail.com

22 anos

SKILLS

TypeScript/JavaScript

Node.js

React.js

Angular.js

Git e Github

Docker

SQL e NoSQL

Next.JS

Team Work

LANGUAGES

Portuguese - BR

Enalish

Spanish

RESUME

Information System student at IFG, currently junior developer of web applications. I have experience with NodeJS from building APIs to Web Automation, using SQL and NoSQL databases, creating containers in Docker and building websites in React.

EDUCATION

Degree on Computer Information Systems

Goiânia, GO - Brazil

fev. 2020 - Present

IFG - Instituto Federal de Goiás

EXPERIENCE

SVA Tech,

Full-Stack Developer,

Belo Horizonte, MG - Brazil

nov. 2022 - Present

• Maintenance and creation of new features of the company's web system. Mainly using Javascript, NodeJS, MongoDB and AngularJS.

Hyerdev,

Web Developer Junior,

Goiânia, GO - Brazil

dez. 2021 - nov. 2022

- Rest APIs development using Node.is.
- Implementing websites in ReactJS.
- Development of web automations using the puppeteer library and docker.
- · Creating custom CMS.

Web Developer intern,

set. 2021 - dez. 2021

• Work in small web development projects with HTML, CSS and Node.js.

ILION Soluções Web, **Customer Support Intern,**

jun. 2021 - aug. 2021

Goiânia, GO - Brazil

- Wordpress maintenance.
- Customer service and support activities.

COURSES

The complete React Developer Course, Andrew Mead - Udemy

ago. 2022

The complete Node.js Developer Course, Andrew Mead - Udemy

out. 2021

English Language and Global leadership, New Jersey City University

nov. 2017 - dez. 2017

ADDITIONAL ACTIVITIES

Exchange, Goiás without borders

New Jersey - USA

nov. 2017 - dez. 2017